<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="game_description_confirm">Close</string>
    <string name="free_game_description">Free game is the simplest version of the game, which has several players. The game master can add points to any player in any order.</string>
    <string name="simple_game_description">Simple game is the main option for most board games. Players have an order in which they can act. The game master can add points to the current player and pass the turn to the next player.</string>
    <string name="dice_game_description">"Dice": each player gets the points they have thrown on the dice, according to the conversion rules. The number of received points is always a multiple of five. It is necessary to score exactly 1000 points. If a player has points in the range from 200 to 300 or 600 to 700, then he is in a special situation ("on the barrel"). Now, in one turn, he must gain points on all the dice, while points can only be added once.</string>
    <string name="carcassonne_game_description">Carcassonne is a strategy board game for 2 – 5 players. The game consists of step-by-step collecting the playing field and placing your subjects\' chips on it. Depending on which area the chip is placed on, it becomes a knight, a peasant, a monk, or a robber. After the player has put up another "square" of the field, he can put one of his subjects on this square. The figures return to the player after their object is completed. Chips placed on the field earn points as soon as the object they occupy is completed. The game ends as soon as all the squares run out. After that, the points are calculated for the remaining chips on the field. The player with the most points wins.</string>
    <string name="monopoly_game_description">Monopoly is an economic and strategic board game for two or more people. The goal of the game is to rationally use the initial capital to remain the only player who has not reached bankruptcy. It is a playing field consisting of squares that all players take turns passing in a circle. The squares are divided into assets and events. When it is the player\'s turn to walk, he determines by rolling a dice how many steps he must take on the playing field during this turn.</string>
</resources>